Now that we've talked about tab navigator as well as our stack navigator,
我们已经讨论了 TabNavigator 和 StackNavigator
the last navigator we need to discuss is the DrawerNavigator,
最后一个要讨论的导航器是 DrawerNavigator
which is going to allow us to route using a drawer which
它使我们能够使用在屏幕左侧或右侧
pops out either on the left or the right hand side of the screen.
弹出的抽屉式导航栏浏览应用
So you'll notice here that we have two components.
这里有两个组件
And now in each one of these,
现在 在这些组件中
instead of just routing from
我们不再像之前那样
the home component to the dashboard component as we've seen before,
从 Home 组件转到 Dashboard 组件
what we're going to eventually do is we will have this button and when we click on it,
最终我们将添加这个按钮 点击该按钮后
no matter which route where in,
无论位于哪个页面
it's going to open the drawer so that we can navigate to the other route.
都会打开抽屉式导航栏并转到其他页面
So the very first thing we want to do is,
首先转到这里
let's come in here and we will create our drawer component,
并创建 Drawer 组件
which is going to be the result of calling DrawerNavigator.
将其设为调用 DrawerNavigator 后的结果
So the very first route,
第一个页面
as we've seen before,
正如之前看到的
is going to be our home route.
将是 Home 页面
The screen is just going to be home.
screen 设为 Home
And then we will have the dashboard route and
然后是 Dashboard 页面
the screen is going to be the dashboard component.
screen 设为 Dashboard 组件
So now what we need to do,
现在要做的是...
because React Navigation is rendering both of these views,
因为 React Navigation 正在渲染这两个视图
it's going to be past navigation as we've seen in the past.
它将被传入 navigation 正如之前看到的那样
So what we can do here,
在这里
is when this touchable opacity component is pressed,
当这个 TouchableOpacity 组件被点击后
what we can do is we can call navigation.navigate.
我们可以调用 navigation.navigate
And now what we want to do is pass in the string drawer open.
然后传入字符串 DrawerOpen
And what this is going to do,
这段代码的作用是
is it's going to open the drawer,
打开抽屉式导航栏
which we will see here in a minute.
稍后在这里会看到
So now we have it both on our home component as well as our dashboard component.
现在 我们在 Home 组件和 Dashboard 组件中都添加了导航栏
And now the last thing we need to do is just render our drawer that we created.
最后 我们需要渲染刚刚创建的 Drawer
So now, you'll see here we have our home view.
现在 这里出现了主屏幕
And we can open the drawer and we get the drawer pop out.
我们可以打开抽屉式导航栏 直接弹出来了
And now, we can navigate between our two routes using the drawer.
我们可以使用抽屉式导航栏在两个页面之间切换
So let's go ahead and add a few alterations just really quickly.
我们快速添加一些修改
What I want to do is I want an icon to be shown in the drawer itself.
我们希望在抽屉式导航栏中显示图标
So we as we've done before can add some navigation options.
和之前一样 添加一些导航选项
We'll say, drawer label is going to be home and then
将 drawerLabel 设为 Home
we will say drawer icon is going to be a font awesome icon.
将 drawerIcon 设为 FontAwesome 图标
The name is going to be home.
name 设为 home
We'll say a size of 20 and we'll give it
size 设为 20
a color of black and then now I'm just going to copy and paste these down here.
color 设为 black；将这些代码复制粘贴到这里
Now instead of home we will call this dashboard and we will change this to dashboard.
将 Home 改为 Dashboard 将这个改为 dashboard
So now what should happen when we open the drawer is we
现在 当我们打开抽屉式导航栏时
should see these icons right here.
应该能够看到这些图标
And we can still navigate between the two components.
并且依然能够在这两个组件之间切换